这夜店是我的梦想
This club is the dream.
不得不说 我对此印象深刻
I have to admit I'm impressed.
你把这里打理得很好
You run a smooth operation here, James.
我们相遇时 你觉得我会成为什么样的人?
When we met, who'd you think I was gonna be?
纽约最大毒枭
The biggest goddamn drug dealer in New York City.
那天你来夜店肯定有什么事
Must be a reason you came in the club the other night.
我给你看一样东西 我给我们各拿了一个
I got you something, one for each of us.
谁能提供人名 地名或者日期
Who can give us the names, places, and dates
来指控洛沃斯?
we need to convict Lobos?
我们得营业 否则洛沃斯就会采取行动
We gotta open up this store, or Lobos will move on.
我发了通缉令逮捕鲁伊斯的助手
I issued a warrant for a Ruiz Lieutenant,
诺马・阿奇斯罗
Nomar Arcielo.
你想让我背叛费利佩・洛沃斯?
You want me to rat on Felipe Lobos?
直到你听到诺马还打给谁了
Wait till you hear who else Nomar called.
伊莎贝尔・鲁伊斯
Isabel Ruiz.
伊莎贝尔・鲁伊斯的女儿?
Isabel Ruiz's daughter?
她不是只有14岁吗?
Isn't she 14?
如果我们办得干净利落 我们就能高枕无忧
We do it right, it'll shut this shit down for good.
- 如果不能呢? - 那我们就要打一场仗
- And if it doesn't? - Then we go to war.
我去?
What the fuck?
杰米:
干嘛呢?
安琪:
为梦想献身
Livin' the dream.
还有将近五百人在门口排队
The line should be 500 people long.
我刚刚把另一袋现金锁进保险柜
And I just took another bag of cash to the safe.
这是今晚第三次了
Third time tonight.
安琪:
今晚生意如何?
- 还不赖吧? - 挺好
- Good, huh? - Not bad.
和周六晚上比如何?
How's that compare to saturday night?
那倒比不上
I mean, it doesn't.
说实话 这只是周二
To be fair, though, it's a tuesday.
杰米:
很棒
我去找点毒品 好吗?
I'm gonna go find us some blow, okay?
让我们嗨起来
Get this party started.
我是不是在哪见过你?
I know you, don't I?
你是不是演员或者模特?
Are you an actress or model?
我登上了上个月的《Maxim》杂志
I was in Maxim last month.
只有两页通版的珠宝广告
Just a two-page spread, accessories.
我记得 我很喜欢
I remember. I liked it.
你是不是很想嗨起来?
So you really wanna party?
要不要过来玩?
Wanna come through?
给你带了你要的
Grabbed that org chart
洛沃斯贩毒集团的组织关系结构图
of the Lobos cartel you asked for.
你想先吃还是先干活?
You wanna eat or work first?
你真的相信洛沃斯
You really think Lobos only meets his distributor
每年只见他的经销商两次?
twice a year?
我觉得我们应该
I was thinking we should take another look
再好好研究联邦调查局的记录
at the Federales' records.
怎么了?
What?
你还有第三种选择
You're inspiring a third option.
有什么不对吗?
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
弗兰基希望我能集中精力
Frankie warned me to stay focused.
- 嗯 - 我们还是干活吧
- Mm-hmm. - We should work.
嗯 我们一会再做
Mm-hmm. We will.
过一会
After.
我觉得
I was thinking
洛沃斯肯定有个代理人帮他...
Lobos must be using a proxy for his...
进行定期联络通信
Regular communication.
噢 太爽了
Oh, shit, that's amazing.
那让我试试
So move over then.
好啦 等等 马上就到你了
All right, hold on. Wait your turn.
我琢磨着
But I was thinking,
如果我们增加到每周开五个晚上
if we open up a fifth night every week,
那我们能赚更多 得到更多曝光
it's that much more money, that much more exposure.
太多曝光 就变成过度曝光
Too much exposure. It's called over-exposure.
就让五百人在外面等着
Make the 500 people wait.
怎么了?
What?
- 救命! - 噢 我的天呐!
- Help! - Oh, my God!
- 快醒醒 - 滚开! 塞布丽娜!
- Wake up. - Fuck off! Sabrina!
- 我的老天爷 - 塞布丽娜!
- Oh, my God. - Sabrina!
- 快把急救人员带来! - 有人能帮忙吗
- Get the medics now! - Somebody help me.
出去
Out.
让人把门锁了
And have someone block the door.
把人带到楼上女士休息室
Redirect traffic to the women's room upstairs.
- 求求你快醒醒 - 她吃了什么?
- Please wake up. - What did she take?
宝贝 听着 听我说
Sweetheart, listen to me. Listen to me.
她吃了什么?
What did she take?
吸了可卡因 但她就吸了两条
Blow. Coke. But she only did two lines.
你确定?
Are you sure?
可卡因 混了些别的东西
Cocaine, cut with some bad shit.
- 嘿... 女士? - 快来人救救她!
- Hey, hey, hey, ma'am? - Somebody help her!
醒醒 醒醒!
Wake up, wake up!
进行胸部按压
Start compressions.
- 我差点也吸了 - 二 三...
- I almost did a line. - Two, three...
- 噢 天呐 - 四 五 六 七 八
- Oh, my God. - Four, five, six, seven, eight.
- 她会没事吧? - 有脉搏了
- Is she gonna be okay? - I got a pulse.
吉姆 把救护车叫来
Yo, Jim, bring an ambulance around.
好了 听我说
Okay, listen to me. Look.
楼下会有救护车等着你们
There's gonna be an ambulance downstairs,
你们俩都去医院 好吗?
it's gonna take both of you to the hospital, okay?
等你到了医院
When you get to the hospital,
他们会问你怎么回事
they're gonna ask you what happened.
不 不 不!
No. No, no!
不 我什么也不能说 她妈妈会杀了她的
No, I can't say anything because her mom will kill her,
- 那就... - 听着
- and it'll be... - look.
如果你不说实话 她也会死
If you keep your mouth shut, she'll die anyway.
是因为劣质可卡因
It was bad coke.
就是这么回事 你就这么告诉他们
That's what happened. That's all you have to tell 'em.
和你说了我们这些急救医疗技术员请得值
Told you having our own emts was worth every penny.
如果我们干等着911来
Ten minutes we would've waited for 911,
十分钟内她早死了
she'd be dead already.
此外 没警察 没狗仔 简直不能更明智
Plus, no police, no press. No one's the wiser.
还有你 都是劣质可卡因那一套?
And you, all that bad coke shit?
真是绝了
Impressive.
我给你来一杯 老板
Let me grab you a drink, boss.
- 我戒酒了 - 你还是要庆祝一下
- I don't drink anymore. - Still you should celebrate.
上一次你救了一条人命是什么时候?
When's the last time you saved a life?
我去
Fuck.
你瞧 安多芬让世界变得更美好
See, endorphins make everything better.
安多芬不能帮我们抓住洛沃斯
Endorphins don't help catch Lobos.
如果你半裸着还能思考工作
And you're half-naked and still thinking about work.
我不知道是该郁闷还是应该佩服你好
I don't know whether to be offended or impressed.
我去?
What the fuck?
你之前没接警署打来的电话
You got a relay call from the office.
现在轮到我了
There goes mine.
看来我们得赶紧起床
Looks like we're up.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
我孤枕难眠
Bed's awfully empty.
你很快就回家吗?
You coming home soon?
是 很快
Yeah, soon.
今晚有些离谱 有个女的吸食了劣质可卡因
Had a crazy night here. Girl got some bad coke.
她死里逃生 但是...
She lived, but...
不是我们的货
Not our product.
塔莎 我们不在这卖货
Tasha, we don't do that here.
那还有啥问题? 快回家来
Then what's the problem? Come home.
好 我这里的事一处理完 我就马上赶回家
Yeah. Soon as I'm done here, I'll come straight home.
好的 再见 宝贝
Okay. Bye, baby.
真他妈老古董 他希望在这里和我们碰头?
Fucking classic. He wanted to meet us here?
我知道你有你的任务
I know it's your task force,
但严格来说他还是我的线人
but he's technically my C.I.
我们有条约的
There's a protocol.
所以一会我来问 我来写报告
So I'll lead the interview, write the report.
你在暗示什么?
What are you insinuating?
我没暗示什么 小姑娘
Not insinuating anything, cowgirl.
我是说我们都心知肚明
I'm saying we both know
你会走捷径并取得成功
you'll cut corners to get a win.
在法庭上 这没问题
In the courtroom, it's fine.
但是在这... 要守规矩
But there are rules in the field... follow them.
人来了
Here we go.
婊子!
基佬
Maricon.
见到你真高兴 宝贝
Good to see you too, homey.
你们来这干嘛?
你有没有什么信息可以提供给我们的?
What do you got for us?
你们想把我暴露了吗?
这街区的白人 是人都知道你是条子
我只和那个女巫谈
很高兴再次见到你 宝贝
他说他不会告诉你的
He says he's not talking to you.
嗯 我猜到了 谢谢
Mm. Yeah, I got the gist, thanks.
你打电话给我们
You called us.
我以为你会提供些费利佩・洛沃斯的消息
So I assume you have some information on Felipe Lobos...
一些视频 音频之类的
you know, some sort of video, audio recording,
或许一两张照片 或者...
maybe a photograph or two, or...
一个消息... 谁帮洛沃斯卖毒品
A tip... who sells Lobos' drugs
什么时候卖 怎么卖
and when and how it happens.
- 是的 我有消息给你 - 嗯
- Yeah, I got your tip. - Mm-hmm.
后面有个人在贩毒
我们就有话直说了
你是我们的线人 不是别的
你下次还敢用这些破理由半夜把我们叫出来试试看?
我就把你交给鲁伊斯处置 你个淫棍
听见没?
悉听尊便
你他妈去哪了 ?
Where the fuck you been?
还以为你死在那里了呢
Thought you died in there.
狂野之夜啊 伙计
Wild night, man.
我们得谈谈 正经事
We got business to discuss, real business.
好吧 说吧
Okay, go.
自从我们把尸体碎片送到城里
Retail side's been locked up tight
零售已经没人了
since we sent those body parts around town.
后天我们就会
We're getting a big distro shipment coming in
有个大单
day after next.
毒品交易点那边怎么样?
How are the corners?
老他妈安静了
Pretty fucking quiet.
所有人都知道我们重新上位 又回来了
Everyone knows a re-up's coming.
他们会一直盯着我们
They'll be watching us.
是时候了 告诉胡里奥
It's time. Tell Julio.
我们去兜兜风 你亲自告诉他吧
Let's take a ride. Tell him yourself.
得回家了 塔莎在等着我呢
Nah. Gotta get home. Tasha's expecting me.
我们得换掉那个被邮差砍伤的姑娘
Oh, we gotta replace the girl who got slashed, the courier.
胡里奥已经搞定了 白人小妞 声音像黄雀
Julio already handled it. White chick, nice tits.
- 我一会去找你 - 一会儿见
- I'll catch you later. - Later.
汤米告诉我
Tommy told me you got shook
你那天晚上看砍人被吓到了
at the chop shop the other night.
我还好
I was good.
我第一次见到砍人
First chop shop I saw,
一个家伙的头掉了 就在地上滚啊滚
dude's head fell, rolled across the floor
就像他妈的保龄球
like a goddamn bowling ball.
把我都吓尿了
It scared the shit out of me.
- 实际上你爸爸也在那里 - 他也在?
- Actually your pops was there. - He was?
其实承认你被吓到了也没关系的 肖恩
It's okay to admit it fucked you up for a minute, Shawn.
那时他就这样对我说
And he said it to me,
所以现在我也这样告诉你
so I'm saying it to you.
是卡南教我如何掌控这样的场面
It was Kanan who taught us how to hold a saw.
他教你的? 天呐
He did? Jesus.
我不知道他竟然和汤米一样
I didn't know he was like Tommy.
停到路边
Pull over.
看着我
Look at me.
没有人和汤米一样
Ain't nobody like Tommy.
我会和他说的
I'll talk to him.
我不想让你也成为这样的人
I don't need you being a part of the game like that.
告诉你爸我会照顾你的
Told your father I'd take care of you.
我老爸从来都他妈的不知道照顾我
My pops doesn't know shit about taking care of me.
你得去看看他 孩子 别随便下结论
You need to go see him, kid. Don't judge him.
卡南为了生存必须那样做
Kanan did what he had to do to survive.
我们都是
We all do.
安琪 你今天有什么计划?
坎托斯:
看到邮件了吗?
我们得尽快找到对策
快点 懒虫! 我们约好十点
Hurry up, sleepyhead! Our appointment's at 10:00.
好吧 我今天不能和你一起去了
Yeah, I can't go with you today.
昨晚那两个女孩
The thing that happened last night
在俱乐部发生的事情...
at the club with the girl...
我知道你不是认真的
I know you ain't serious.
- 这是本月的第一次 - 我知道
- It's the first of the month. - I know.
我们穿着得体 走进去 都有记录可查
We dress nice, we go in, all on the books.
我们去见银行家们
We meet with the bankers.
这个布莱克夫妇企业的烂主意是你出的
This Mr. and Mrs. Black enterprise shit was your idea.
对 但是我觉得你可以搞定 数学队
Yeah, but I think you can handle it now, math team.
你的人穿制服吗?
Did you guys wear uniforms?
我就不应该告诉你这事的
I should've never told you about that.
你会一直提起的
You can never let it go.
拜托 幽灵 我们总是一起去的
Come on, Ghost, we always go together.
我不想一个人
I don't wanna go alone.
我得去俱乐部 宝贝儿
I gotta go to the club, baby.
你是个聪明的女孩
You are a smart girl.
能搞定的
You got this.
我和诺克斯特工一起
I accompanied agent Knox
见了我们的线人诺马・阿奇斯罗
to meet with our C.I. Nomar Arcielo.
我认为他是我们调查
I think he's gonna be a great asset
洛沃斯经销商的绝佳突破口
in our search for Lobos' distributor.
他看起来不可靠
He seemed evasive.
他需要些激励 是这样的
He need encouragement, sure.
奖励是不起作用的
Encouragement isn't gonna do anything.
像诺马这样的街头混混 啥都不知道
Street soldier like Nomar doesn't know shit.
我们应该从普莉美拉成员下手
We should be honing in on the Primeras
他们才有洛沃斯的货
who get Lobos' product.
我们只知道鲁伊斯是普莉美拉的成员
The only Primera we know is Ruiz.
是的 不过还有很多
Yeah, but there are more.
我们找到他们 就可以找到经销商
We find them, they lead us to the distributor.
- 这里你说了不算 - 我说了算
- It's not your call. - It's my call.
诺克斯特工 跟踪诺马
Agent Knox, follow up with Nomar.
还值得再找他一次 说不定还能榨出些什么
It's worth one more visit if we can squeeze something out.
我们继续跟进
We're on it.
如果你们俩对开始钓大鱼
If you two are so confident,
这么有信心
start your search for the big dogs.
就看看你们能找到些什么吧
See what you can unearth.
敬请期待
Looking forward to it.
- 早上好 老板 - 坎托斯
- Morning, boss. - Kantos.
"前途辉煌的嫩模"
"Which fresh-faced, up-and-coming model
在"肉库区新开的最火的夜店"吸白粉
"almost died while powdering her nose
险丧命
"at the hottest new club in the Meatpacking District?
"绝对真实"
This story's no lie."
我知道我说过室内吸粉
I know I said having in-house medics
可以缓解我们过大的压力
would help us to avoid bad press,
但是卫生间里到处都是喝醉了的女人
but the bathroom was full of drunk women.
我倒想知道 谁在我的店里卖粉给她?
What I wanna know is, who sold her blow in my club?
还是不纯的 超差 廉价粉
Bad, fucked-up, stepped-on blow.
吸毒是夜生活的一部分 老板
Drugs are part of the game, boss.
人们都想要派对 要嗨
People wanna get high and party.
我们尽力去控制
We do our best to control it,
但是这就是这生意的一部分
but it's part of the business we're in.
你需要控制进来的人 还有时间
You need to control who gets in here, period.
现在那些警察知道这里卖白粉
So now that the cops know drugs are getting sold in here,
他们会直接派人来
will they send 'em in straight up
还是便衣先来调查 还是别的
or plainclothes cats or what?
我知道你了解他们的工作流程
I know you know how they work.
他们 呃...
They, uh...
通常是直接来
Come in the front door, usually.
四处搜查 跟我们扯皮
Sniff around, they mess with us,
说我们对公众健康造成威胁 让我们关门
call us a public health menace, we get shut down.
在我们和辛西娅・谢里丹签约之前
Before we get Cynthia Sheridan to sign a contract,
就关门了 人们继续生活 休想
we get shut down, people move on, no way.
老板 就像你说的一样 我知道警察怎么办事
Like you said, boss, I know how the cops work.
让我给你看点东西
Let me show you something.
明早你和维克多出货
Shipment tomorrow morning, you and Victor.
- 收到 - 好的
- It's on. - All right.
刚才走进去的是莉莉安娜吗?
That's Liliana who just walked in?
- 是的 - 哇噢
- Yeah. - Wow.
还真他妈的是个笨蛋啊
That is one fucked-up grill.
嘿 朋友 不过她收银干的不错 伙计
Hey, Dog, she's doing good with the count, though, man.
真高兴她还能有件事干的不错
Glad she's good at something,
因为没有人还想和她来一发了
'cause ain't no one gonna fuck her again.
我敢打赌 有一天她会告密的
I'd bet my dick she's gonna snitch someday.
你想我现在就把她带走吗?
Yo, you want me to take her out right now?
不用
Nah.
我们自己找运货人
We find the dealer ourselves
直接把他送货到纽约警察局
and deliver him straight to the NYPD.
我才不拍切┨踝
I don't fuck with cops.
好吧 不过你应该理他们的
Yeah, but maybe you should.
我们支援他们工作 他们抓到犯人
We save them work, they get an arrest,
然后放我们一马
and they leave us alone.
这是什么?
What's this?
我有每个来真相人的名字
I've got the names of everyone who's stepped foot in Truth.
进门的时候我们就扫了他们的驾照
We swipe their licenses at the door.
不是吧
No shit.
名字 生日 身高 体重 发色
Name, birth date, height, weight, hair color.
- 地址? - 没错 还有地址
- Address? - Address, yeah.
驾照上的所有信息
Anything on a driver's license.
我在找有没有熟悉的名字
I was looking for any familiar names
来缩小我们的搜索范围
to narrow down our search.
那天我知道了很多毒贩子
I know a lot of dealers from back in the day.
这是从开业那天开始的吗?
This go all the way back to opening night?
是啊 知道我们知道那个家伙
Yup, so until we find this guy,
我觉得我们咨询下律师
I think we should consult a lawyer.
我是说 我不想这女孩读到这篇报道
I mean, I don't want this girl to read the post,
到了发薪日 就想要起诉
see a payday, and try to sue.
我有个人选 要预付定金...
I got a guy on retainer, and...
我认识一个律师
I know a lawyer.
他很擅长处理这类事情
My guy specializes in this stuff.
我知道了
I got it.
你用我们的钱买的科技股...
That tech stock you bought with our money...
太冒险了 不是吗?
risky move, isn't it?
是的 考虑到你的投资组合规模
Yeah, well, given the size of your portfolio,
所以我并不担心
I wasn't really so worried.
那些清洗工作似乎让你和圣帕特里克先生
Those wash 'n folds really seemed to pay off for you
获益匪浅
and Mr. St. Patrick.
这就是这个生意的成功之处 亚历克斯
That's why it's a great business, Alex.
人们总有不可告人的秘密
People always have dirty laundry.
欢迎 圣帕特里克夫人
Welcome, Mrs. St. Patrick.
请签名
Please sign in.
搞什么啊?
What the fuck?
一切都还满意...
If everything's satisfac...
调出那该死的签名记录
pull up that goddamn log.
坎托斯说他认识一位律师
Kantos said he knew a lawyer,
我告诉他 我有更好的选择
I told him I had a better option.
我通常不做面对面的咨询
I don't usually do in-person consultations,
但仅此一次 我会破例
but just this once I'll make an exception.
噢
Oh.
我对那天的事感到很抱歉
I'm sorry about the other day.
你要工作 我了解
You had to work. I get it.
但确实感觉你总是逃去某个地方
But it does feel like you're always running off somewhere.
你会觉得我现在已经习以为常了
You'd think I'd be used to it by now.
不会让我轻易逃掉 对吗?
Not gonna let me off that easy, are you?
是的
Nope.
所以你觉得那女孩真的有案件发生?
So you think the girl really has a case?
不要用"案件"来形容
Let's not use the word "case."
作为一名律师 我根本不应该在这
Look, as a lawyer, I shouldn't be here at all.
但作为朋友 我想说
But as your friend, I'd say,
有人在你的俱乐部过度用药 你的责任有限
someone ods in your club, you have limited liability
除非你提供毒品 但很明显你没有
unless you provided the drugs, which obviously you didn't.
所以但我走进那...
So when I get in there...
我想你该和她谈谈
I think you should talk to her,
问她现在感觉如何
ask her how she's doing.
向她展示关怀
Show her you care.
无关摆脱诉讼
It's not about getting out of a lawsuit,
首先是要避免陷入诉讼
it's about avoiding getting into one in the first place.
我的经理觉得我们应该和警察合作
My manager thinks we should work with the cops
找到贩毒者 但是 你知道
to find the dealer, but, you know,
来自我们的"邻居"
coming from our neighborhood,
这并不是个好主意 对吧?
that's a terrible idea, right?
- 未必 - 胡扯!
- Not necessarily. - Shit!
你想一下 纽约警察可是007
Coming up, NYPD was 007.
那些徽章特许他们能够杀人
That badge gave them license to kill.
我们看到警察来了 就会逃跑
We'd see the cops coming, and we'd run.
即使我们只在贩售毒品的街角闲逛 记得吗?
Even if we were just hanging on the corner, remember?
我记得
I remember.
但并不是所有的警察都那样
But not all cops are like that.
让其中一些站在你这边未尝不可
It's not a bad idea to have a few on your side.
- 跟我一起上去 - 不了
- Come up with me. - Nah.
那会让整件事跑偏的
The whole thing goes sideways
如果她觉得你带个律师来掩饰罪行
if she thinks you brought a lawyer to cover your ass,
尽管你稍微这样做了
even though you kind of did.
也对
Yeah.
或许我们可以在电话里聊聊这件事
Guess we could've done this on the phone.
- 你不用跟来 - 是的 我不跟
- You didn't need to come. - Yeah, I did.
我的意思是 你为那间俱乐部尽心尽力
I mean, you've worked so hard for the club,
我只想确保付出的能有回报
I wanna make sure it all works out.
夏敦埃酒在较低级的酒吧间供应
Chardonnay at the lower bar.
香槟供应在最上层 靠近贵宾室
Do champagne up top, near VIP
- 圣帕特里克夫人 - 我丈夫在楼上吗?
- Mrs. St. Patrick. - Is my husband upstairs?
他出去了
He went out.
要我告诉他 你来过吗?
You want me to let him know you stopped by?
这件事你不用管了 我会在他办公室等他
Don't worry yourself about it. I'll wait in his office.
办公室可能上锁了
It's probably locked.
那就给我钥匙吧
Then I'll need the key.
我是詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
I'm James St. Patrick,
就是你...的夜总会的老板
the owner of the nightclub where you...
你感觉如何?
How you feeling?
我母亲正从乌克兰飞往这里
My mother is flying in from the Ukraine.
我的代理机构 他们想我去戒毒
My agency, they want me to go to rehab.
我不敢相信竟然发生这样的事
I can't believe this happened.
你不是第一个嗑药的人
You're not the first person to use drugs.
而且你也不是第一个
And you're not the first person
从混蛋手里买到毒品的人
to buy bad drugs off an asshole.
我觉得好愚蠢
I feel pretty stupid.
这类的糟糕事
This kind of a bad thing,
或许正是让你
maybe it's the push you need to start
开始朝好的方向发展的驱动力
heading in a better direction.
这个混账卖药的 你知道他的名字吗
This asshole dealer, you happen to remember his name,
- 他长什么样子的? - 不知道
- what he looks like? - No.
我不想这类事情发生在其他人身上
I don't want this to happen to anyone else.
格雷格:
你在哪里?
安吉拉:
跑腿 一会儿回来
喂 你 你看见詹姆斯了吗?
Hey, there. Have you seen James?
大老板不在这里
Big boss isn't here yet.
大老板? 那我成了什么?
Big boss? What's that make me?
喂 你叫什么名字?
Hey, what's your name?
那重要吗?
Why would that matter?
我想更了解你 仅此而已
I want to know more about you. That's all.
你想上我
You want to fuck me.
不需要为此而知道我的名字
Don't need to know my name for that.
听着 那我该怎么说?
Hey, listen, what do I need to say here?
我不知道 想到什么其他的吧
I don't know. Come up with something.
再见 老板
See you later, boss.
她到底是怎么回事?
What the fuck is her problem?
她是个贱人
She's a bitch.
所以你也是我们其中一个老板?
So you one of my bosses too?
是的
I am.
我是汤米 你的名字是?
Tommy. And your name is?
- 多米尼克 - 多米尼克
- Dominique. - Dominique.
那么你喜欢在这工作吗 多米尼克?
So you like working here, Dominique?
好吧 她现在满脑子只剩下起诉了
Yeah, suing was the last thing on her mind.
她只是个受惊的孩子
She's just a scared kid.
你说跟她谈谈是对的
You were right about talking to her.
住院护士 请回复
Resident nurse, please page out.
作为感谢 让我请你吃午餐吧
Let me buy you lunch as a thank-you.
我不能 我要走了
I can't. I gotta go.
工作上的事情出问题了
Things are blowing up at work.
又是这样
Again.
- 那天在博物馆里... - 嗯哼
- That day in the museum... - Mm-hmm.
我老板告诉我不要分心了
My boss told me not to get distracted.
但不知为何 一扯上你...
But somehow, when it comes to you...
那就留下啊
Well, then stay.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
我们独处一会儿
Be alone for a while.
我也想 但是...
I want to, but...
再见 杰米
bye, Jamie.
我们想我们该转移一下注意力
We thought we'd shift our focus.
阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯是泰诺人兄弟
Anibal Santalises is a Primera
创立的Sangre Fuerte下的一员
of the Sangre Fuerte set of Hamanos Tainos.
被我们盯上是因为上星期
Came onto our radar because last week
他收到了一个特别的投递
he received a special delivery.
一只断裂了的人脚
Severed human foot.
- 天啊 - 你们在说什么?
- Shit. - What are you talking about?
你一个礼拜都在讨论这个?
You sat on this for a week?
我的情报人员才刚回来
My contact just got back to me.
这上面写满关于洛沃斯的事
This has Lobos written all over it.
那只是纯粹的推断
That's pure speculation.
我在街上的情报人员
My contacts on the street
相信鲁伊斯也收到同样的附属肢体
believe that Ruiz got sent an appendage too.
我们都知道鲁伊斯跟洛沃斯有关系
We know Ruiz is connected to Lobos,
或许阿尼巴尔也是
so maybe Anibal is too.
这太荒谬了 我不会批准这个的
This is ridiculous. I didn't authorize this.
我批了
I did.
虽然这是推测 但值得采取进一步行动
It's speculation, but it's worth following up on.
做得好
Nice work.
我能跟弗兰基独处一会吗?
Could Frankie and I have the room?
我真的很希望你先告诉我你批准了这件事
I really wish you told me you authorized this.
我必须加入这场调查的环节当中去
I need to be in the loop on this investigation.
你在这 正式来说 你参与每个环节
You're here. You're officially in all loops.
让我来问问你 你在这的目的是什么?
Let me ask you this. What is your goal here?
- 我不懂你的意思 - 你瞧?
- I don't know what you mean. - You see?
我给你机会去说
I gave you an opportunity to say,
"成功起诉费利佩・洛沃斯"
"the successful prosecution of Felipe Lobos."
你在这不是为了抨击萨克斯和萨克斯
You're not here to beat Saxe or Saxe.
我们都在这 我们所有人一起
We're here together, all of us,
把那个该死的贩毒者送进监狱
to put a fucking drug dealer in jail.
任何一个让我们接近这个结果的行动
Any move that gets us closer
都是好的 对吗?
to that result is the best move, right?
是的
Right.
诺马那边呢 你有得到什么新信息吗?
And with Nomar, you have anything new?
那就是我所想的
That's what I thought.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
谢谢
Thanks.
扁平足真是可恶
Flat feet are a bitch.
你该庆幸遗传了你妈的
You're lucky you got your mama's.
你的医生跟你说什么了吗?
So you got any news from that doctor you been seeing?
还是那一套
Nothing new.
他说了什么?
Well, what'd he say?
没有进展
No improvement.
治疗没有用 我的膝盖永远粉碎了
The treatment didn't work. My knee's busted for good.
那就换个医生 这才六个月
Then find another doctor. It's only been six months.
我总得面对现实 爸 我再也不能打篮球了
I gotta face it, pops. I can't ball anymore.
你也要面对这一点
So you gotta face it too.
那你别的还忙什么?
So what you doing instead?
我找了份新工作
I got a new job.
给幽灵叔叔开车
Driving Uncle G.
对了 他要我向你带个好
And he says hey, by the way.
你出去后
When you get out,
他给你的经销权都准备好了
he's got a whole franchise all ready for you.
我一直 我一直知道这一天会来的 伙计
I always... I always knew this day would come, man.
他对你好吗?
He treat you right?
挺好的
Yeah, he does.
他也总是跟我讲你的事...
He keeps telling me about you too...
你教会他的东西
what you taught him,
你们以前多么亲密
how close y'all were.
我猜我还有很多要学的
I guess I got a lot to learn.
听着 不管你何时想聊聊
Listen, if you ever need to talk about some shit going down,
你不能对幽灵讲
some shit you can't tell Ghost,
纵火者 守卫们不让我闲着
burner. Guards keep me stoed.
我就知道你会让我骄傲的 儿子
I know you gonna do me proud, son.
好吧 咱们走
All right, let's go.
走吧
Let's go.
走走走
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
要么过来搭把手 要么滚一边去
Help the fuck out, or fuck the fuck off.
好吧
All right.
你觉得我们今天早上
What, do you think we're hosting
在这儿是开派对的吗?
a party here this morning?
没有 我上了个卖甜甜圈的妞
Nah, I'm fucking the doughnut chick.
你能搞到免费的甜甜圈?
And you get free doughnuts?
有啊 想要多少有多少
Shit, yeah. As many as I want.
我也能跟她来一发吗?
Think I could bang her too?
走吧
Let's go.
- 还是平时下车的地方? - 那当然
- Usual drop? - No doubt.
好的 我猜也是
All right, bet.
甜甜圈很好吃的 兄弟
Doughnuts are good, man.
伙计 你和那些该死的甜甜圈 还有狗
Man, you and those fucking doughnuts, dog.
马上滚出去
Get out of the fucking car, now.
举起手来
Hands up.
放下枪
Put it down.
你也滚出来 站到墙边
You too, get the fuck out. By the wall.
走走
Let's go.
好啦 兄弟 冷静一点行吗?
All right, man, hey, calm the fuck down, all right?
你给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
转过去
Turn around.
我只想用车 不会害人的
I just want the van. Nobody's got to get hurt.
我可不这么看
That's not the way I see it.
依我看来 你会饱受摧残
The way I see it, you're gonna get hurt real bad,
除非说出我需要的信息
unless you tell me what I need to know.
诺马・阿奇斯罗有没有打电话? 我...
Has Nomar Arcielo called in? He hasn't answered my...
诺克斯特工刚才联系了他几次 他都没接
agent Knox's last few attempts to make contact.
他肯定认识这个号码
Of course he recognizes the number.
只不过故意不理睬
He's ignoring us on purpose.
诺马 马上接电话
Nomar, call in now.
去死吧 该死的协议
Fuck this. Fuck protocol.
喂
Yeah.
找到那个人了 维克多货已到手
Got the guy. Victor's got the product.
我们需要知道是谁 谁派他来的
Okay, we need a name, who sent him,
他们怎么知道在哪儿能找到我们
how they knew where to find us.
我正在办
I'm on it.
你没带肖恩一起去 对吗?
You don't got Shawn with you, do you?
- 我是没带 - 好吧
- Nope. - All right.
我知道在仓库里
I know you liked popping his cherry
你想让他染指杀人的活
on the wet work in the warehouse,
但我想让你暂时别这么做
but I want you to lay off for a while.
我还想让你把那个叫多米尼克的姑娘
And I want you to move that Dominique girl
划入俱乐部贵宾之列
to the VIP Section at the club.
她很棒
She's good.
哪方面?
Good at what?
我说过别招惹推销员 汤米
I told you not to touch the merchandise, Tommy.
幽灵 我们得谈谈
Ghost, we need to talk.
我得去俱乐部了 宝贝
I got to get to the club, babe.
超级惊喜
Big surprise.
想知道我要干什么吗?
You want to know what's going on?
我要去找到那个卖药的
I'm trying to find the dealer that sold that girl
他卖给那姑娘的破玩意差点要了她的命
the bad shit that almost killed her,
我们可以把他交给警方
so we can turn him over to the cops.
你现在成了告密者?
So now you're a snitch?
这就是你所在意的?
That's what you take from all that?
- 爸爸 - 没事的 宝贝 没关系
- Daddy. - It's okay, baby. It's okay.
我要管公司... 我们得让警察高兴
I got a business to run... we keep the cops happy,
他们就不会找我们麻烦了 就这样
which keeps 'em off our backs, that's it.
从你认识你以来
As long as I've known you,
你从来没有担心过惹到警察
you ain't never been worried about keeping no cops happy.
你现在想这么做吗?
You want to do this right now?
不想
Nah, I don't.
好了 宝贝
Okay, baby.
来吧 小甜心
Come on, honey.
咱们去找外婆
Come on, let's go find big mama.
我要处理点事情
I got some business to take care of.
知道吗 每次我说这种话
Every time I say something like,
"快交代你为谁卖力"
"tell me who you're working for,"
都觉得自己在演老电影
I feel like I'm in an old movie, you know?
就像他妈的阿尔・卡彭在那边
It's like fucking Al Capone over here.
美国知名罪犯
- 卡彭? - 是的
- Capone? - That's right.
喂
Hey, hey.
你最喜欢哪个黑帮?
Who's your favorite gangster of all time?
卢西亚诺吗?
Luciano?
是埃斯科瓦尔吧?
Escobar, right?
人人都爱看经典
Everybody loves the classics.
那么
Okay, then.
老实交代你的幕后主使
Tell me who you're working for,
不然的话我们就来玩一玩
or we're gonna have a little fun.
你好
Hola.
这可是个意外惊喜
我只用监视
All I had to do was look
离你家最近的天主教学校
for the closest catholic school to your house.
你知道我在找你
You know I've been looking for you.
我很忙
可我欣赏你的努力
把你对阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯知道的一切都告诉我
你的朋友 那个好战的特工
他吓得我都不举了 懂我的意思吧?
可你的话...
我觉得只有我们两个人的话 或许能得到一些结果
你我都清楚 我对你太老了
阿尼巴尔 泰诺人兄弟
从来没听说过
既然我们已经跑题了...
不如来玩一玩 你意下如何?
停下
Stop.
喂 汤米 伙计 算了吧 朋友
Hey, yo, Tommy, man, come on, dog.
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
再等一秒钟
Give him another second.
你把我们赶下车后
What were you supposed to do with the van
准备做什么?
once you got it off us?
我应该把它开到布鲁克林的一个停车场
I was supposed to drive it to a parking lot in Brooklyn,
停车走人
park it, and walk away.
谁会来把它开走?
Who was supposed to pick it up?
得了 赶紧说
Hey, yo, man, talk.
给你十秒钟
You got ten seconds.
一 二 三 四...
One, two, three, four...
五 六 七...
Five, six, seven...
好好
Okay, okay.
好好好
Okay, okay, okay.
她说...
She said...
她? 还是个女的?
she? It was a woman?
她... 她说我们在为某个家伙干
Sh... she says we were doing it for some guy.
我不知道他叫什么
I don't know his name.
那就向你的小伙伴告别吧
Then say good-bye to your little friend.
看见我在那边做的事了吗? 疤瘌脸
You see what I did there? Scarface.
笑一个 畜生
You should've laughed, motherfucker.
她叫他大胖子
She called him El Gordo.
是阿尼巴尔
That's Anibal.
听着
Esteombre...
阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯
别和我废话 诺马
他有和鲁伊斯联系过吗?
他有和洛沃斯联系过吗?
我不知道你在说什么
你最好在受伤前回家去 女巫
没错
You're right.
我还是个有证的女巫
I am a bruja with a badge.
你要继续和我胡闹 我可以很冷血地
You keep fucking with me, I can shoot you in the street,
把你当街射杀 然后说是正当防卫
in cold blood, say it's self-defense.
没人会他妈眨一下眼睛
No one will bat a fucking eye.
所以你得和我说说上周
So you're gonna talk to me about this guy
那个收到一个包裹里面有只脚的人
who got a fucking foot in the mail last week.
我必须知道这是他妈的什么事 诺马
I need to know what the fuck is going on, Nomar.
我要知道我在应对什么
I need to know what I'm dealing with.
那个人收到了一只脚?
That guy got a foot?
我听说鲁伊斯收到了一个头
I heard Ruiz got a head.
根据受害者说
According to the victim,
那个卖药的是个深色头发 五官鲜明 高个
our dealer is dark-haired, clean-cut, tall...
中等身材
basically your average pinstripe prick.
他的名字是斯科特 好了 事情就是这样
His first name is Scott. All right, here's the deal.
我们需要每个人都睁大你们的双眼 每个人
We need everybody to keep their eyes open. Everyone.
姑娘们 如果你们有看到有谁
Ladies, if you catch this piece of shit in action
在这里卖这种东西 把他交给我
selling this bullshit in here, you hand him over to me,
然后我会给你们一笔很优厚的报酬
and I hand you back a big, fat bonus check.
一夜工资的双倍
Double a night's pay.
哦 还有 不择手段 这没有规则
Oh, and do whatever it takes. There are no rules.
都听到了吧
You heard him.
好了 去干活吧 开门迎客...
All right, let's get to work. Open the doors...
不择手段 啊?
do whatever it takes, huh?
我猜你终究还是没变啊
Guess you haven't changed after all.
我们要谈谈 就现在
We need to talk. Now.
塔莎 不管你想了到什么
Tasha, whatever's gotten into you,
我们还是回家再谈吧
we're gonna talk about it at home.
这是我工作的地方
This is my place of business.
你工作的地方是我唯一能抓住你注意的地方
Your business is the only place I can get your attention.
我去了银行
I went to the bank.
我看了金库
I saw the vault.
你认为我会注意不到?
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
你觉得我会注意不到你拿了什么?
Did you think I wouldn't notice what you took?
我要花这笔钱开夜店
I had to use that money to open the club.
这必须要是我们合法账户里的现金支票
It had to be a cashier's check from our legit account.
总不能给那些国家机关的酒囊饭袋
Couldn't give the state liquor motherfucker
用可卡因换来的灰色收入
a stack of hundreds covered in coke dust.
而且事实是 塔莎 那是我的钱
And truth is, Tasha, it's my money.
你竟然说这种蠢话 幽灵
Don't you dare start that shit, Ghost.
我帮你挣了每一分钱
I helped you earn every goddamn penny.
你本可以预先告诉我
You could've told me up front
这个俱乐部会花多少钱
how much this club would cost.
你本该说清楚的
You could've said something.
但你让我像个傻瓜一样去银行
But you sent me into that bank like boo-boo the fool
却不知道你在做什么
don't know shit about what you're doing.
你看到了我们在那里赚了多少钱
You saw how much money we got in there.
我们不是没有破产的危险
We ain't in no danger of going broke.
这和钱没关系
It ain't about the money.
你什么时候开始对我说谎了?
Since when do you lie to me?
你什么时候开始对我有所隐瞒了?
Since when do you hide shit?
我觉得你不会理解
I didn't think you'd understand.
你为什么不试试?
Why don't you try me?
我是一个聪明的女人 记得吗?
I'm a smart girl, remember?
我这么做是为了我们所有人
I'm doing this for us.
- 这是我们的逃离计划 - 逃离什么?
- It's our escape plan. - Escape from what?
我不知道 那些年老的毒贩
I don't know any old, wrankled drug dealers.
他们要么死了 要么牢里去了 塔莎
They're either dead or inside, Tasha.
你没觉得怕吗?
That doesn't scare you?
没有
No.
因为他们不是你
Because they're not you.
他们没你优秀
They're not as good as you.
这间夜店就是一个梦想
This club is the dream.
我们能脱身 我们能拥有一切
We can get out. We can have it all.
我们已经拥有一切了
We already have it all.
你 我 还有孩子们
You, me, the kids.
现在的情况和生活 就是我的梦想
The way things are now, it is my dream.
我觉得我们找到他了 老板 那个斯科特
I think we got him, boss. Scott.
我得走了 塔莎
I gotta go, Tasha.
他符合基本描述
He fits the physical description,
还是对相同类型的女孩下手
is preying on the same type of girl.
已经检查过他的身份证刷卡记录了
Already checked his I.D. swipe.
他那天晚上在这里
He was here that night.
别废话
No shit.
- 他有卖东西吗? - 还没
- Did he sell any product yet? - Nope.
好的 一旦他卖 我们就抓住他
All right, well, as soon as he does, we'll grab him.
- 好的 - 等一下
- All right. - Hold on.
- 怎么了 - 那个孩子开口了
- What's up? - The kid talked.
你最好过来一下
You better get your ass out here.
好的 我要走了 伙计
Yeah. I got to go, man.
- 你要走了? - 是的
- You got to go? - I got to go.
好吧 你要我怎么做?
Well, what do you want me to do?
霍莉 给我盯着那个家伙
Holly, I want you keep your eye on that prick.
试着让他卖药给你
Try to get him to sell to you.
我会搞定的
I'm on it.
打电话给我
Call me.
一旦他有任何分吹草动 电话我
Soon as he makes a move, call me.
了解
Got it.
他不肯告诉我他为谁工作 现在我们知道了
He wouldn't tell me who he was working for. Now we know.
好吧
Okay.
你把我叫醒 拖我出屋子 为了什么?
You wake me up, drag me out my house, for what?
你雇了这个混蛋来偷我东西?
You hire this motherfucker to boost my product?
当然不是 我从没见过他
Fuck no. I never seen him before.
你说过你不知道
You told me you didn't know nothing
我们为什么受袭
about us getting hit,
阿尼巴尔 你当着我的面说过
Anibal, you said it to my face.
可我们从这个"香酥牛肉"听到的可不一样
We're hearing a different story from crispy beef here.
结果是一直都是你幕后操控的
Turns out you were behind it the whole fucking time.
喂 我干嘛要这么做?
Yo, why the fuck would I do that?
喂 幽灵 你了解我的 伙计
Yo, Ghost, you know me, man.
- 我以为我了解 - 喂
- I thought I did. - Yo.
你准备因为这个畜生的话
You gonna do me like this
就要对我这样?
on the word of this motherfucker?
给我跪下
Get on your fucking knees.
要是你把一个人点着了 他会用一种
People have a funny way of telling the truth
很滑稽的方式告诉你真相
when you light 'em on fire.
晚安 阿尼巴尔
Nighty night, Anibal.
你这撒谎的畜生! 艹!
喂 幽灵 你知道 要是我
Yo, Ghost, you know that if I'm gonna
想算计你 我应该用我最得力的人
fucking step to you, I'ma use my best men.
这畜生不是泰诺人
This motherfucker ain't Taino.
我是被冤枉的
Yo, I'm being set up.
我用我的孩子们发誓 伙计
Yo, I swear on my kids, man.
我们在浪费时间 做了他
We're wasting time. Do him.
汤米 要是你雇人来干这样的活
Tommy, if you hire a hitter to pull off a job like this,
你要确保他是把好手
you gotta make sure it's someone good.
米格尔隐瞒实情 然后说是这孩子干的
Miguel hid the shit and then talked, this kid broke.
是的 我吃一堑长一智
Yeah, well, I learn from my mistakes.
也许吧 胡里奥 把他弄醒
Maybe. Julito, wake him the fuck up,
然后问再问问他怎么接到这活的
and ask him again how he got the job.
喂喂喂 醒醒
Hey, hey, hey. Wake the fuck up.
嘿
Hey.
哦 老板?
Yo, boss?
这货死了
Yo, this motherfucker's dead.
我以为我让他四分熟
I thought I cooked him medium rare.
我发誓我没做过
I swear I didn't do nothing, yo.
- 罗拉要我陷入窘境 - 那都是废话
- Rolla wants my corners. - That's fucking bullshit.
鲁伊斯讨厌我 因为我是多明尼加人
Ruiz hates me 'cause I'm Dominican.
- 毙了这个畜生! - 我不会杀一个人
- Shoot this motherfucker! - I ain't gonna kill a Primera
除非我有证据证明他出卖了我
unless I got proof he's crossed me.
- 这就是你的证据! - 想想看 汤米
- There's your proof! - Think, Tommy.
要是阿尼巴尔在这里被冤枉了
If Anibal's being set up here,
我们也被人算计了 挑起争端
so are we, to start a fucking war.
我另有计划
I got another plan.
- 我们停止业务 - 什么?
- We shut everything down. - What?
我们要开一个会
We have us a meeting.
我坐在桌子对面
I sit across the table,
我要看着所有人的眼睛
I look all those motherfuckers in the eye,
然后找出是谁打压我 一劳永逸
and I find out who's hitting me, once and for all.
在此之前 没人能拿到货
Until then, no one gets product.
- 把话传下去 - 幽灵
- Spread the fucking word. - Ghost.
幽灵 我们不能光停下批发业务
Ghost, we can't just shut down the wholesale business.
我们不能让那个胖子就这么一走了之
We can't just let fat Albert go.
我们想怎么样还能办不成吗
We can do anything we want to do.
我们需要证据 汤米
We need proof, Tommy.
但要是阿尼巴尔从头到尾搞的鬼
But if I find out it was Anibal all along,
我保证亲手了结他
I promise you, I'll cut his throat myself.
你没打电话
You didn't call.
那妹子钓了他一晚上 他也不搭茬
The girl was on him all night. He never dealt.
要是条子打电话来 我们好好表现
Look, if the cops call, we play nice.
能抓住掮客则锦上添花 前程一片大好
Grabbing the dealer was icing. It'll all work out.
好消息 今晚赚了八万多
Good news, we made upwards of 80k tonight.
好极了
Pretty fucking great.
霍莉 要不要帮你打车?
Hey, holly. Can I get you a cab?
好的 谢谢
Yes, please.
要不要送你回家?
You want a ride home?
姐穿着六寸高跟鞋走了九个小时
I just spent nine hours in 6-inch heels, so...
但还不至于走不动路
Getting down on my knees ain't gonna happen.
不是那样的 霍莉
It's not like that, Holly.
哟呵 你不辞辛苦终于知道我的名字了
Mm, you took the trouble to learn my name.
厉害吧?
You impressed?
个屁
Nope.
你上次跟妹子约会是什么时候啊?
When was the last time you asked a girl out on a real date?
你到底知不知道怎么约?
Do you even know how?
我能不能带你去吃早点 霍莉?
Can I take you to get some breakfast, Holly?
晚安
Good night.
老大
Boss.
昨晚上又是一大波电话
Bunch of calls went out late last night.
线人说要开会
Connect called a meeting.
线人叫什么名字?
You got a name for the connect?
什么性质的会?
What kind of meeting?
我当年跟一个泰诺兵是过命的交情
I was inside with a Taino soldier a few years ago.
他欠我一条命
He owes me one.
他说你的弟兄 阿尼巴尔
He says your guy, Anibal,
虽说不知道是不是他召集的
don't know if he called the meeting,
但是他一准会到场
but he's gonna be there for sure.
这下爽了吧?
Are you happy now?
爽翻了
Yes, I'm happy.
抱一个行不?
抱你妹
你得给我弄清楚
I need you to find out when and where
会议的时间和地点
this meeting's gonna be.
诺马・阿奇斯罗已经确信鲁伊斯 阿尼巴尔
Nomar Arcielo confirmed that Ruiz, Anibal,
以及其他洛沃斯在纽约分舵人员
and other members of Lobos' New York network
应经销商之请要召开会议
will be convening at the distributor's behest.
那就是说阿尼巴尔脱不开干系?
So Anibal is involved?
我们什么时候能得知
We'll know how exactly when we get
确切的会议时间和地点
the when and where of the meeting.
我的线人在办这件事
My C.I. is on it.
你说的是诺克斯探员的线人
You mean agent Knox's C.I.
诺马已经回应安吉拉的号召了
Nomar's been responsive to Angela,
所以她得陪我去碰头
so she's been accompanying me on meet-ups,
就跟今天早上一样
like the one this morning.
事实证明对付诺马就不能来善的 想想看吧
Turns out Nomar likes the bad cop. Go figure.
在会上抓住经销商 用他来扣洛沃斯
We catch the distributor at this meeting, flip him on Lobos,
献给柯林斯的漂亮一击 一网打尽
nice little package for Collins, all wrapped up with a bow.
你们俩干得不错
Great work, you two.
谢谢你帮我圆场
Thank you for covering for me.
诺马对你知根知底
Nomar knows your real name.
你家住哪 在哪工作
How hard would it be to find out
想查到不是手到擒来的事情吗?
where you work, where you live?
我家有枪
I have a gun.
有枪管啥用 我还有炮呢
Oh, f... what, you...
你有没有把这玩意放在办公室的许可
you have permission to have it at the office
或者紧急情况使用权?
or time to use it when he busts through your front door?
也许我得在你那儿住一阵子
Maybe I should stay at your place for a while,
- 直到 - 我会小心行事
- until this is... - I'll be careful.
- 好的 - 我保证
- Okay. - I promise.
我得写份报告 我们在哪见诺马?
I gotta write this report, so where did we meet Nomar?
安琪:
请我吃饭吗?
这次能待多久离开?
So how long before you have to split?
- 我没问题 - 没才怪
- I'm good. - Yeah.
老娘干了一早上的活
I had a good morning at work,
所以奖励自己一下 跟你一起吃薯条
so I'm rewarding myself with these fries and with you.
告诉我出了什么事吧
So tell me what happened.
要我实况播报会议内容吗?
A play-by-play of my meeting?
那你要多喝点咖啡来保持清醒
Hmm, you better get more coffee to stay awake.
有那么枯燥吗?
That bad, huh?
你那边呢? 那个经手人抓到没?
What about you? Did you catch that dealer?
像昨天那样的情况 安琪 我是说
Days like yesterday, Angie, I mean...
尼玛
Shit.
让我在想这一切是不是在自己捉弄自己
Makes me wonder if I'm kidding myself doing all this.
- 一切什么? - 全部 所有事
- All what? - All of it, everything.
为有今天的成就所做的一切决定
All the choices I've made to get here.
听我说
Listen, hmm?
我不知道经营夜店要怎么样
I don't know what's involved in running a club,
但我知道我的工作就是这样 简而言之
but I know that at my job, let's just say,
今天万人敬仰
one day I'm the hero,
明天就可能万人唾骂
the next day I'm knee-deep in shit.
我就是这么想的
That's exactly how I feel.
但我还不至于放弃 你懂吗?
That doesn't mean I give up, you know?
有些人无需付出努力 一切都能手到擒来
Some people get everything handed to them on a platter.
如此这般只要花点小钱
All they have to do is count their money.
但我从来不是这样的人
That's never been me.
从来没人送我钻石或者给我付租金
No one's ever bought me diamonds or paid my rent.
我曾经自己买了个手镯
I bought myself a bracelet once.
帕斯却已经有人买好给她了
Some guy got one for Paz,
我买不起真正的手镯
but I couldn't afford the real version.
带着那玩意把我的手都变绿了
Turned my whole arm green.
但我一直戴着那个手镯 直到它碎掉
But I wore it till it fell apart.
我和你一样 从来都是自力更生
I've always done everything for myself, like you.
我们靠着自己才爬到今天的地位
We got ourselves where we are.
- 感觉好孤单 - 孤单的很
- It gets lonely. - Lonely.
不是所有人都能理解我们的 杰米
Not everybody understands us, Jamie.
这也是我坐在这里陪你的原因 安琪
Guess that's why I'm sitting here right now with you, Angie.
安琪 巴尔德斯
Angie Valdes.
你现在不孤单了吧?
You don't feel lonely now, do you?
不了
No.
我觉得这次是我要孤单了 不 是你要孤单了
I think maybe this time I did. No, you did.
怎么回事?
What happens now?
天知道
I don't know.
这次你跑不了
But I'm not letting you go again.
有事电话联系
I'll call you.
打不打还难说呢
You better.
拿着这个
Here, take this.
我老爸向你问好
My pops said hello.
是吗? 看到他感觉怎样?
Yeah? How was it seeing him?
还可以
Fine.
应该说挺好的吧
Maybe good.
我九岁的时候他就进局子了
He's been in since I was nine,
这件事让我耿耿于怀
and I always hated him for it.
但是今天我觉得很愧疚
But after today, I feel guilty.
我来去自由 做事随意
I'm out here on easy street, doing whatever I wanted.
虽然现在跟你一起工作
But now that I'm working with you,
我父亲则不一样
I see my dad differently.
他虽然不甚完美 但还是我爹
Sure, maybe he's not perfect, but he's my father.
我猜你大概就是那个意思吧?
I mean, isn't that what you meant?
我得休息一下
You know what, I need to make a stop.
回家吧
Head uptown.
提前回家了啊
You're home early.
你骗我 幽灵 这玩意什么也弥补不了
You lied to me, Ghost. These don't make up for shit.
那就还回去呗
Give 'em back, then.
亚斯明睡着了 替我看着她
Yasmine's down for her nap. Keep an eye on her.
塔莎
Tasha!
怎么了? 到底啦?
What is it? What is it?
宝贝 宝贝
Baby, baby.
给我 这是什么?
Give me. What is it?
你没事了
You're okay.
- 她没事了 - 你没事了
- She's okay, she's okay. - You're okay, you're okay.
- 我说了她已经没事了 - 你没事了
- Hey, it's okay, she's okay. - You're okay.
她嘴里是什么鬼玩意?
What the hell is that in her mouth?
好了
It's okay. It's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
都没事了 没事了 宝贝
It's okay, baby. It's okay. It's okay.
妈妈在 没事了
I got you. I got you. It's all right.
没事了
It's all right.
你是安吉拉・巴尔德斯?
You Angela Valdes?
在这里签字
Sign here, please.
我勒个去 这是
My God. Oh, my...
嘘 没事啦 有我呢
shh. We're fine. I got you.
有我在呢
I'm here.